Were you okay during this time?
この間大丈夫だったでしょうか?
I did it the other day.
この間やったね
You always did it.
いつもやったね
Isn't it good?
いいでしょ?
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Isn't it good?
いいでしょ?
why?
なんで?
sorry.
ご め んなさい
ごめんなさい
sorry.
Okay.
いいよ
Because I'm going out.
外出すから
Are you going up with me?
一緒に上がるの?
Do you get growth between your fingers?
お前、指の間生えちゃうの?
Just wait a minute.
ちょっとしろって
You can't see if it's grown, right?
生えちゃったか見えないでしょ?
They say the lower mouth won't grow.
下の口は生えないって言ってるぞ
I'll move on my own.
自分で動くよ
Shall we move together?
一緒に動く?
Okay.
いいよ
Be proud of yourself.
お前、自慢にしろよ
It feels good.
気持ちいいよ
I'll let you know, I'll let you know.
口出すから、ベラ出すから
Why don't you cum?
なんで中出さない?
No way.
だめだね
When can I go?
いけるよ、いつに
If you eat more.
もっと食べれば
I'm hungry.
お腹すいた
Is it okay?
いいの?
It's okay, I don't care.
いいって、別に
That's what I do all the time.
やってるのが、いつも
I hid it in my face.
顔にかくしちゃったよ
No.
だめ
Get it out.
出せ
is
だ
eye.
め
Why not?
なん でだめって
It's really complicated.
すっごいこっかかってるね
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
Don't take my face.
俺の顔取んなよ
Where do you want it?
どこに欲しい?
Where is it?
どっかでしょ?
Isn't it good?
いいでしょ?
That's gold.
あれ、金
This is fine.
これでいいんだよ
Isn't it fun?
楽しいんだろ?
Wipe it off with this.
これで拭いとけよ
That's nice.
いいな
Is that wrong?
違うか
That's what I'll do next time.
次はやるときはあれ
Because I'm hungry.
お腹すいたから
Any time is fine.
いつでもいいよ